Can you clarify for me what people are referring to when they state that Democrats and Republicans are two wings of the same bird?
Well, basically what it means is that Republicans and Democrats, though they may carry out certain behaviors that are different from each other,
ultimately serve the same goal, which is to keep corporations in power and to keep the central banking system as an imperial ruler, collecting and stealing all the resources of the world.
Who do you mean when you're referring to the Epstein class?
So the Epstein class refers to, let's call it a cult of people who have essentially traded in their basic human civility,
which means, you know, not eating babies, in order to attain a certain level of power in the world.
And that power is what allows them to not face any consequences for the terror that they are reigning over the world.
What's a Zionist?
A Zionist is somebody that believes that Israel should exist, regardless of the fact that it was supplanted onto land that was occupied by folks for multiple generations, representing multiple religions.
Hey, what are old heads talking about when they say hip hop ain't like it was back in the day?
We basically mean that for the most part, the hip hop of today is low vibrational and makes no effort at trying to educate and elevate people on a mainstream level.
If you got any truths you want me to translate, get your mug at AmandaLandXSports.com.
Bye-bye.
Pause it, my little shot.